# Wan Muhammad Irfhan

E-mail: wanirfhan@gmail.com Mobile Number: (+60)194091242

Address: No. B24, Lorong ½, Taman Seri Mesra, 08100 Bedong Kedah, Malaysia

# PERSONAL PROFILE

A highly motivated Mechanical student graduated from Cardiff University with 1 year of industrial experience in engineering field. Dedicated to pursue technical and administrative work in Engineering Company to further expand my knowledge and eager for international experiences.

# RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

# 2012 – 2013 Silterra Malaysia – Process Engineer

- Ensured that the Etch tool is in perfect condition for production by using monitoring software for analysis and maintained the quality of the process.

#### **EDUCATION**

(2008 - 2012)

**Cardiff University,** Cardiff, Wales, UK MEng Mechanical Engineering (Hons) – 2:2

#### **Projects List:**

Group project:	Designed a fully functional wind turbine model with real location (Cardiff
	Bay) covering all aspects of design planning; from business model, designing,
	fabrication and construction. My role was to the design transmission system
	and to create construction plan
Individual project	Developed a tidal turbine model construction using CFD Software (ANSYS
	FLUENT) to analyze water flow around the turbine blade surface under
	different water velocity and to monitor the wake created by the turbine blade.

(2007 - 2008)

College Mara Kulim, Kedah, Malaysia

Foundation Year - CGPA: 3.75 (Awarded top 15 students of the year 2007)

# OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

(2008 – 2012) Malaysian Students Society of Cardiff (MSSCF) – IT Director

- In charged of leading, organising and producing media coverage and technical aspects of various large scale student events (ranging up to 800 students).
- Involved in the organization of events as a member of the society committee
- Events: Leadership conference, Festival of Diversity and Cardiff European Games

#### **SKILLS**

- Ansys FLUENT
- Nastran Patran
- MATLAB
- Solidwork
- HTML
- SPACE

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Winner of chess competition in 2008.
- Second place in web design Cardiff University in 2012.
- Winner for Best Society in 2011.

#### HOBBIES AND INTEREST

- Web Site Designing maintained the student society website throughout the two years
- **Photography** provided media coverage for large scale events
- Badminton
- Wall climbing